[
    {
        "question": "artista",
        "options": ["umělec", "herec", "tatínek", "kolo"],
        "answers": ["umělec"]
    },
    {
        "question": "attore/attrice",
        "options": ["umělec", "herec/herečka", "zpěvák/zpěvačka", "fotbalista"],
        "answers": ["herec/herečka"]
    },
    {
        "question": "babbo",
        "options": ["tatínek", "čokoláda", "lyžař", "zpěvák/zpěvačka"],
        "answers": ["tatínek"]
    },
    {
        "question": "bicicletta",
        "options": ["kolo", "motorka", "město", "kravata"],
        "answers": ["kolo"]
    },
    {
        "question": "calciatore",
        "options": ["fotbalista", "hudební skladatel", "zpěvák/zpěvačka", "básník"],
        "answers": ["fotbalista"]
    },
    {
        "question": "cantante",
        "options": ["zpěvák/zpěvačka", "herec/herečka", "tatínek", "fotbalista"],
        "answers": ["zpěvák/zpěvačka"]
    },
    {
        "question": "capisce",
        "options": ["rozumí", "rozumíš", "město", "kaučuk"],
        "answers": ["rozumí"]
    },
    {
        "question": "capisci",
        "options": ["rozumíš", "rozumí", "tatínek", "město"],
        "answers": ["rozumíš"]
    },
    {
        "question": "caucciù",
        "options": ["kaučuk", "zlato", "čokoláda", "lyžař"],
        "answers": ["kaučuk"]
    },
    {
        "question": "chirurgo",
        "options": ["chirurg", "politika", "fakulta", "město"],
        "answers": ["chirurg"]
    },
    {
        "question": "ciao",
        "options": ["ahoj", "čokoláda", "město", "fakulta"],
        "answers": ["ahoj"]
    },
    {
        "question": "cioccolato",
        "options": ["čokoláda (nápoj)", "lyžař", "zpěvák/zpěvačka", "zlato"],
        "answers": ["čokoláda (nápoj)"]
    },
    {
        "question": "città",
        "options": ["město", "tatínek", "kravata", "umělec"],
        "answers": ["město"]
    },
    {
        "question": "come",
        "options": ["jak", "kaučuk", "fotbalista", "zpěvák/zpěvačka"],
        "answers": ["jak"]
    },
    {
        "question": "compositore",
        "options": ["hudební skladatel", "básník", "lyžař", "fakulta"],
        "answers": ["hudební skladatel"]
    },
    {
        "question": "costruttore",
        "options": ["konstruktér automobilů", "chirurg", "tatínek", "město"],
        "answers": ["konstruktér automobilů"]
    },
    {
        "question": "cravatta",
        "options": ["kravata", "fakulta", "zpěvák/zpěvačka", "čokoláda"],
        "answers": ["kravata"]
    },
    {
        "question": "facoltà",
        "options": ["fakulta", "město", "umělec", "fotbalista"],
        "answers": ["fakulta"]
    },
    {
        "question": "genio",
        "options": ["génius", "lyžař", "fotbalista", "zpěvák/zpěvačka"],
        "answers": ["génius"]
    },
    {
        "question": "giornalista",
        "options": ["novinář", "zpěvák/zpěvačka", "básník", "fakulta"],
        "answers": ["novinář"]
    },
    {
        "question": "gnocchi",
        "options": ["noky", "lyžař", "fakulta", "čokoláda"],
        "answers": ["noky"]
    },
    {
        "question": "gondola",
        "options": ["gondola", "město", "lyžař", "kravata"],
        "answers": ["gondola"]
    },
    {
        "question": "gusto",
        "options": ["chuť, vkus", "zpěvák/zpěvačka", "město", "lyžař"],
        "answers": ["chuť, vkus"]
    },
    {
        "question": "mamma",
        "options": ["maminka", "tatínek", "zpěvák/zpěvačka", "básník"],
        "answers": ["maminka"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mediterraneo",
        "options": ["Středozemní moře", "fakulta", "město", "umělec"],
        "answers": ["Středozemní moře"]
    },
    {
        "question": "motocicletta",
        "options": ["motorka", "kolo", "město", "tatínek"],
        "answers": ["motorka"]
    },
    {
        "question": "oro",
        "options": ["zlato", "kaučuk", "čokoláda", "město"],
        "answers": ["zlato"]
    },
    {
        "question": "personaggio",
        "options": ["pohádková postava", "zpěvák/zpěvačka", "město", "kravata"],
        "answers": ["pohádková postava"]
    },
    {
        "question": "pizza",
        "options": ["pizza", "čokoláda", "tatínek", "umělec"],
        "answers": ["pizza"]
    },
    {
        "question": "poeta",
        "options": ["básník", "novinář", "zpěvák/zpěvačka", "lyžař"],
        "answers": ["básník"]
    },
    {
        "question": "politico",
        "options": ["politik", "novinář", "umělec", "město"],
        "answers": ["politik"]
    },
    {
        "question": "questo",
        "options": ["tento, toto", "ahoj", "lyžař", "zpěvák/zpěvačka"],
        "answers": ["tento, toto"]
    },
    {
        "question": "regista",
        "options": ["režisér", "zpěvák/zpěvačka", "město", "tatínek"],
        "answers": ["režisér"]
    },
    {
        "question": "rivoluzionario",
        "options": ["revolucionář", "zpěvák/zpěvačka", "básník", "umělec"],
        "answers": ["revolucionář"]
    },
    {
        "question": "sciatore",
        "options": ["lyžař", "fotbalista", "básník", "zpěvák/zpěvačka"],
        "answers": ["lyžař"]
    },
    {
        "question": "scrittore/scrittrice",
        "options": ["spisovatel/spisovatelka", "zpěvák/zpěvačka", "novinář", "fakulta"],
        "answers": ["spisovatel/spisovatelka"]
    },
    {
        "question": "scusi!",
        "options": ["promiňte!", "ahoj", "tento, toto", "zpěvák/zpěvačka"],
        "answers": ["promiňte!"]
    },
    {
        "question": "signore/signora",
        "options": ["pán/paní", "tatínek", "novinář", "fotbalista"],
        "answers": ["pán/paní"]
    },
    {
        "question": "slovacco",
        "options": ["slovenský", "zpěvák/zpěvačka", "město", "lyžař"],
        "answers": ["slovenský"]
    },
    {
        "question": "spaghetti",
        "options": ["špagety", "noky", "čokoláda", "básník"],
        "answers": ["špagety"]
    },
    {
        "question": "telefonano",
        "options": ["telefonují", "rozumíš", "zpěvák/zpěvačka", "město"],
        "answers": ["telefonují"]
    },
    {
        "question": "università",
        "options": ["univerzita", "fakulta", "město", "zpěvák/zpěvačka"],
        "answers": ["univerzita"]
    },
    {
        "question": "vino",
        "options": ["víno", "čokoláda", "zpěvák/zpěvačka", "lyžař"],
        "answers": ["víno"]
    },
    {
        "question": "zero",
        "options": ["nula", "fakulta", "tatínek", "zpěvák/zpěvačka"],
        "answers": ["nula"]
    },
    {
        "question": "capitale",
        "options": ["hlavní město", "region", "mapa", "země"],
        "answers": ["hlavní město"]
    },
    {
        "question": "carta geografica",
        "options": ["mapa", "moře", "hora", "obec"],
        "answers": ["mapa"]
    },
    {
        "question": "fiume",
        "options": ["řeka", "země", "hlavní město regionu", "moře"],
        "answers": ["řeka"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Italia",
        "options": ["Itálie", "hlavní město regionu", "region", "hora"],
        "answers": ["Itálie"]
    },
    {
        "question": "mare",
        "options": ["moře", "hora", "mapa", "každý"],
        "answers": ["moře"]
    }
]
